xpertswiki.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Xperts Wiki collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [Xperts Wiki](http://xpertswiki.com/ "Xperts Wiki") website. This privacy policy applies to the Site.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences only when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a social or ad popup once in your visit, or the ability to register/login to some of our features.

We also use third party advertisements on blogdum.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our blog, and in some cases, whether you have installed Adobe Flash . This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by changing preferences in programs such as Kaspersky, Norton,etc. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

**How we use collected information**

XpertsWiki may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service

Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

  * To personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

  * To improve our Site

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

  * To send periodic emails

If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We strictly follow Google Adsense policies and we don’t allow any ads and links to websites which disobeys Google Adsense policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google Privacy Policy").

**Compliance with children’s online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Xperts Wiki has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us [here](http://xpertswiki.com/contact/ "Contact Us").

This document was last updated on February 03, 2013.
